LOST剧情回顾
Previously on Lost...
我们每一个人被带到这里来都是有原因的 -那么是谁把你带到这里的?  John
Each one of us was brought here for a reason.-And who brought us here, John?
岛
The island.
这是命运
It's destiny.
你和你的拍档负责观察
You and your partner will observe
一个正在进行的心理试验
a psychological experiment,in progress.
你们的责任是观察岛上的另一组成员
Your duty is to observe team members in another station on the island.
他们不知道自己被监视以及自己是试验品
These team members are not aware that they are under surveillance
以及自己是试验品
or that they are the subjects of an experiment.
我渺小可悲的生命中的每一秒钟都和那个按钮一样没用
Every single second of my pathetic little life is as useless as that button!
你坚持按下去我们都不会自由
As long as you push it,we'll never be free.
既然你坚信那是骗人的就别按那个按钮
If you're so sure it's not real,then just stop pushing the button.
我当然没有按了不幸的是  另外一个人要按
Well, I have, except, unfortunately,someone else decided to start.
明天我们要查清楚如果不按按钮会发生什么事情
Tomorrow we're gonna find out what happens if that button doesn't get pushed.
这个拳击手是谁?
Who is he, Box Man...
在外面敲门的那个? 他的名字叫Mr.Eko
the man out there pounding on the door? His name is Mr. Eko.
-为什么Mr.Eko带着一个刻着圣经片段的棒子? -因为他是一个神父
Why does Mr. Eko carry around a stick covered
in scripture? -Because he's a priest.
-我们必须按按钮-不  没必要
- We need to push the button.- No, we don't!
那是真的  快按那个按钮
It's all bloody real! Now push the damn button!
你害死我们了
You've killed us all.
不  我救了我们
No, I just saved us all.
(系统错误)
System failure.
我错了
I was wrong.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： Singa 后期：梁良 双语字幕：不二色的鱼
John什么时候回来的?
When John get back?
他在干什么?
What's he doing?
他刚才到哪里去了?  其他人在哪里?
Well, where's he been?Where's everyone else?
你去问一下他好吗?
Don't you think you should go find out?
从舱门那里发生爆炸算起
So you're gone for a whole day
你失踪一天了
after a massive hatch detonation.
你不给我们打电话
You don't call,
也不给我们写信
you don't write.
对不起  我打扰你了吗
Sorry. Am I interrupting something?
什么?  你--
What, you...
你不能说话?
you can't speak, John?
你哑了?
You're mute?
我很抱歉
I am sorry about that.
Eko和Desmond在哪里?
So where are Eko and Desmond?
他们和你一样哑了而且在盖小屋吗?
Are they off being mute and building structures as well?
我知道  你不能说话
I know. You can't speak.
你想说话吗?
You need to speak.
对我说?
To me? What do you want to...
沙子?  你想和沙子说话?
The sand. You need to speak to the sand.
树?  不错  它们很健谈
Trees. Yeah, I've heard they're wonderful conversationalists.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你到底想和谁说话
Who do you need to speak to?
教堂...天空?
The... church. Sky.
岛
Island.
你想和...
You need to speak...
岛说话
to the island.
迷失
第三季 第三集
"我需要你帮忙"
"I need your help."
你怎么会需要我帮忙?
Since when do you need my help?
"我需要你帮我站哨"
"I need you to stand guard."
知道了  你需要我保护你和岛说话
Oh, yeah, so you can talk to the island.
听起来很危险
Yeah. Sounds dangerous.
装哑巴真好玩
Well, amusing as the mute game invariably is...
你是个聪明人  John你知道我讨厌你  对吧?
You are aware, John, that I detest you, aren't you?
记得你以前打我
You do remember repeatedly punching me in the face
和胡乱指责我逞英雄吗?
and accusing me of using heroin when I was not?
"sweat lodge"是什么意思?
What the sodding hell is a "sweat lodge"?
-你要去哪里? -Eureka
Where you headed? Eureka.
我可以载你一程  送你到Bridgeville那里
Well, I can get you as far as Bridgeville.
来吧  上车
Come on, hop in. Come on.
-我叫John -Eddie
- My name's John.- Eddie.
-你好 Eddie  -你好
- Hi, Eddie.- Hey.
-这天气太烦人了 -对啊
- Nasty day to be hitching.- That's for sure.
如果你不介意我想问问你到Eureka去干什么
If you don't mind my asking,what's in Eureka?
我听说那里能找到工作  有伐木场之类的
I heard there was some work there,cutting timber.
你伐木工吗?
Is that what you do?
可能吧  还没定下来
That might be what I do. I don't know.
我必须出来工作
All I know is that I had to get out of where I came from.
妈妈死了爸爸又酗酒
Mom's dead, dad's a drunk.
看  雨停了
Hey, look at that. The rain is passing.
你抢银行了吗?
What, did you rob a bank?
恐怕是
'Fraid so.
能给我看一下你的证件还有驾照吗
Can I see your license and registration, please?
我超速行驶了吗?  Tail light's out.
Was I speeding, officer?
你们两位下车来好吗
Could you both please step out of the vehicle?
车后面装的是什么
What do you got back here?
枪和一些杂货
Guns and groceries.
账本和许可证都在后面
Now the transaction logs and the paperwork
在那个红色的文件夹里面
for all of 'em's in the red notebook right there in that duffel.
我们可以走了吗?
So are we free to go?
我还是可以逮捕你因为你载了一个搭便车的
I could still take you in for picking up a hitchhiker.
他是我舅舅
Oh, that's my uncle.
我叫他送我的
I called him, and he picked me up.
你们可以走了
Get outta here.
这些枪是干什么的?
So what is with all the guns...
舅舅?
uncle?
我喜欢门帘里面那个壁炉
I like the indoor fireplace.
真了不起
It's very snazzy.
那是什么?
What's that?
你不是在...吃药吧  JOHN?
You're not...taking drugs, are you, John?
我只是随便问问
I only ask
因为你的规则太严格了
because of the strict zero-tolerance policy you've enacted.
我不希望你因为乱吃东西
I wouldn't want you to have to start
打自己的脸
punching yourself in the face.
知道了
Yeah, I know.
你会进入你的魔法小屋
I get it. You're gonna go in your little magic hut,
我站在外面防止你变成一只猴子
and I'm gonna stand out here in case you devolve into a monkey.
"别--进来"
"Don't... come in."
好 我知道了
Okay. I get it.
你好 John
Hi, John.
真高兴能再见到你
It's good to see you again.
什么意思? JOHN?
What's that, John?
你很抱歉?
You're sorry.
没关系
That's okay.
我是这个岛要求的祭品
I was the sacrifice the island demanded.
别着急
Don't worry.
你该说话时自然就可以说话了
You'll speak when you have something worth saying.
我来帮你从新找到方向把家人找回来
I'm here to help you find your way again,so
you can bring the family back together.
来吧  我给你看点东西
Come on.I want to show you something.
John
你需要坐轮椅
You're gonna need that.
John  这个机场里有些人现在很危险
John, someone in this airport is in serious danger.
你是唯一可以救他们的人
You are the only one who can save them.
不是他们  他们没事
Not them. They'll be fine...
至少现在是这样
for a while.
我觉得sayid可以帮他们
I think Sayid's got it.
下一位
Next, please.
不是Hurley
Not Hurley.
别管他  他知道该怎么办
Forget it. He's helping himself.
你帮不了他们
There's nothing you can do for them,
现在还不行
not yet.
你得先收拾你自己留下的残局
First,you have to clean up your own mess.
(收拾你自己留下的残局)
Clean up your own mess...
first,you have to clean up your own mess.
(收拾你自己留下的残局)
上来啊John
Come up here, John.
把它擦干净JOHN
Clean it up, John.
他们把他抓走了
They've got him.
你时间不多
You don't have much time.
John
怎么了?
What happened?
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我要去救Mr.Eko
I'm going to save Mr. Eko's life.
Eko的十字架
Eko's cross.
他是从这边被拖走的
He was dragged this way.
拖?  被什么拖?
Dragged?By what?
北极熊
By the polar bear.
Sawyer不是杀了北极熊吗
Sawyer killed the polar bear.
Sawyer只杀了一只北极熊
He killed a polar bear.
那是什么  John  血?
What's that, John, blood?
我自己一个人去  Charlie  你回Claire那边去
I'm gonna go on alone, Charlie.You go back to Claire.
我自己可以做决定
Well, I'll take my chances.
你最好别和我一起  CHARLIE.
You don't want to go with me, Charlie.
我身边的人都没有好结果
Bad things happen to people who hang around with me.
你好  Bobby
Hey, Bobby.
那是什么?
What's that?
那是我们的"sweat lodge"
That, Eddie, is our sweat lodge.
什么?
A what?
人们可以进去点一把火
Anybody who wants can go in there and light a fire
-认真的思考  -然后呢?
and get it nice and hot and meditate. -Then what?
然后你会知道该做什么
And then you're supposed to find what to do
关于你的人生--该选择什么方向
with your life,you know, what-- what direction to take.
进去找到方向
Go on in there and figure out
这里的农民和猎人都喜欢这样
if you're a farmer or a hunter.
你是前者还是后者  John?
So which are you, John?
你好 John
Hey, John.
你好 Mike  Jan  这是Eddie
Hey, Mike. Jan, this is Eddie.
他准备找一份伐木工作
He's looking for some logging work,
我坚持让他到家里来和我们吃顿饭
but I convinced him to come home and have supper with us first.
-很高兴认识你Eddie   -很高兴认识你
- Nice to meet you, Eddie. - Nice to meet you.
John的朋友就是我们的朋友
Any friend of John's is a friend of ours.
没错  John是个很特别的人
Right. John's a very special guy.
找个位置坐下吧
Grab a spot.
你喜欢Geronimo Jackson对吗?
So you like Geronimo Jackson, huh?
对  他们很棒
Yeah, yeah. They're all right.
这是我爸爸以前的衣服
It's one of my dad's old shirts.
你爸爸很有品位
Your dad has excellent taste.
大家注意
Listen up, people.
John带了一位客人来和我们一起吃晚餐
John brought a guest to supper.
这是Eddie
So, everyone, this is Eddie.
Eddie这是大家
- Eddie, this is everyone.
很高兴见到你们
Nice to meet you.
John你来祷告好吗?
John, you want to say some grace?
好
Yeah.
谢谢你  上帝
Thank you, Lord.
谢谢你给我这些食物和朋友
Thank you for the food and the friends,
谢谢你今天下的雨
and thanks for the rain today,
Adam终于可以停止抱怨干旱了
so that Adam will stop grumbling about the drought.
还有谢谢你帮我脱离困境
And for me, thank you for helping me stop being so angry,
然后--
And... and for...
帮助我找到一个真正的家庭
helping me find a real family.
他们比我以前那个家庭好多了
Because they're a hell of a lot better than the one I used to have,
大家开始吃吧  阿门
so let's eat. Amen.
要点土豆吗?
Potatoes?
谢谢...谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
那是个舱口吗?
Is that the hatch?
它怎么变成这样的?
What's left of it.
发生过什么事情?
What happened?
这里看起来好像--
Looks like it...
发生过爆炸
imploded.
是什么?
What is that?
捕食
It's an active kill.
意味着刚才在吃这个的动物
Meaning that whatever was eating this
会带更多同类回来
is coming back for more.
如果你的意思是"北极熊"  说"北极熊"就可以了
If you want to say polar bear,you can just say it.
没错  是北极熊
All right. Polar bear.
快跑
Run!
老兄...
Dude.
他们留下了Jack  Kate  Sawyer
They kept Jack, Kate and Sawyer,
放我回来告诉剩下的人
And they sent me back to tell everyone else
叫我们别到他们的地方去
that we can't ever go over there.
老兄  我在那边的时候看到Henry了
Oh, and that dude we had in the hatch--Henry?
好像是他们的头
He was there. He's, like, their leader.
那么...我们该怎么办
So... what do we do?
照他们说的办
Do what they told you.
回露营地去告诉剩下的人
Go back to the camp and tell the others.
你不采取行动吗?  什么都不做?
You're not gonna do anything?
我正在行动  你回海滩去  HUGO
I am doing something.Go back to the beach, Hugo.
等一下  你们到哪里去
Wait. Where are you guys going?
这个岛告诉Locke他得去救Eko
The island told Locke he has to save Eko.
为什么要救他?
Save him from what?
很显然他被一只熊抓了
Well, apparently a bear's got him.
而且那只熊刚刚还在捕食
It's just made an active kill.
你可能想快点回去了
You may want to hustle.
熊?
Bear?
什么熊?
What bear?
什么?  又是毛吗?
What's that, more fur?
走这边
This way.
有一次我吸毒后
When I used to get high,
看了"BEEB"(电视台)的自然节目
I'd watch nature programs on the "beeb."
节目里面说北极熊很聪明
Polar bears are meant to be quite clever.
非常聪明
Very clever.
他们像是熊里面的--爱因斯坦
They're like the Einsteins of the bear community.
她喜欢你  伙计
She likes you, man.
-嘘  -真的  她喜欢你
Oh, yeah, she does.
-胡说  -真的
- She does not.   - Yeah, she does.
她的年纪只有我的一半  你应该去约她
She's like half my age, man. You'd be better off with her.
不  Lizzie不是我喜欢的类型
No. Lizzie's too granola for me.
她真正需要的是父爱
What she really wants is a daddy.
就像这里其他人一样
Like everyone else here.
你应该利用你的优势
You should take advantage of that.
这很无聊Eddie
That's not real funny, Eddie.
开玩笑而已  只是开开玩笑
It was a joke.It was a joke!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你怎么从来没有说起你父亲John
How come you never talk about your dad, John?
没什么好说的
Nothing worth talking about.
那边在干什么?
What's going on in that greenhouse over there?
我去帮他们搬肥料
Maybe they need a hand with that fertilizer.
不  不  不  他们自己能行
No, no, they're okay. They're okay.
我们还是管好果园
Come on. We got orchard duty.
你们到底有什么秘密John
What's the big secret, John?
什么?
Sorry?
-什么?  -温室
The greenhouse.
你们到底藏了什么
What do you guys got in there? What are you hiding?
每次我走进温室的时候--
'Cause every time I go near it,
你和其他人的表情都很怪
you and everyone else acts all weird.
你是我们的客人  这些事情我们要慢慢告诉你
Look, you're a guest here.These things take time.
我来这里都六个星期了
I've been here for six weeks.
-Eddie  那里什么都--   -我不是瞎子伙计
- Eddie, nothing's--   - I'm not blind, man.
你记得你带我来这里的时候车后面放了一麻袋枪吗
Did you forget that you had a duffel
bag full of guns When you brought me here?
Mike和Jan很欢迎你来
Mike and Jan welcomed you here with open arms.
他们给你吃的
They feed you.
-给你住的地方   -Mike和Jan
- They give you a place to stay...- And Mike and Jan
每次吃饭以前都说我们怎么怎么是一家人
fold their hands every night before chow and talk about how we're family,
但你们之间还有这么多秘密
but your family's got too many secrets.
我看到肥料搬进温室以后终于知道是怎么回事了
Now I see the fertilizer going into that greenhouse.I know what's going on...
而且我想加入你们
and I want in.
加入什么?
In on what?
你们偷偷摸摸干的大事情
Whatever you guys are trying to blow up.
什么事情这么好笑?
What's so funny?
没什么
Nothing.
我和Mike还有Jan商量一下
I'll talk to Mike and Jan.
你真的觉得Eko在这里面?
You really think Eko's in there?
我们快点进去吧
Let's hurry up and do this.
可能熊还在外面吃饭
Maybe the bear's out finishing his lunch.
-你不能进去Charlie   -什么?
- You're not going in there, Charlie.  - What?
我一个人进去
I'm gonna do this alone.
你没必要告诉我我该做什么
You don't tell me what I can't do.
如果我想进去我就要进去
If I want to, I'll go in there.
-为什么?      -什么?
- Why?       - What?
-你为什么想进去    -没有为什么
Why do you want to go in there?
-那就回去  -回去?
- Then go back.  - Go back?
你也没有理由进去
You don't have a good reason to go in there, either.
我要进去因为我应该进去
I'm going in there because I'm supposed to go in there.
按照计划--
If it all goes to plan,
我们应该不会碰到熊  对吗?
we probably won't even see the bear, will we?
希望它不要发现我们
Hopefully he won't smell us.
发胶?  很抱歉
Hair spray? Now I hate to be the one
-我不是针对你  -这不是给我用的
to point this out to you--- It's not for me.
熊?
Bear?
是你吗?
Is that you?
谁在那里?
Who's there?
你是一个人吗兄弟?
Are you alone, brother?
对...是啊
Yeah.
老兄  我不是一个人
Dude. I'm not alone.
露营地就在那边
The beach camp's right over there.
你可以帮我那些衣服过来吗?
Can you get me some clothes?
你的衣服呢?
What happened to yours?
我在丛林里醒来就这样了
I woke up in the jungle like this.
嗯...
So...
你在舱门里面...
like, the hatch...
把内衣炸飞了?
blew off your underwear?
好  你想讨论这些细节我们就开始吧
Fine. You wanna discuss this in great detail right now, let's do it.
不  不  不  不用了
No, no, that's okay.
我这里有衣服
I got something in here.
这件你穿合适吗?
How do you feel about tie-dye?
你好 Kim
Hey, Kim.
Mike和Jan在里面吗?
Hey, Mike and Jan in?
对
Yeah.
他们正在找你
They were looking for you.
看来我来得很及时
Good, good. Good timing, then, huh?
进去吧
Go on in.
-所有的现金都装带齐了吗? -在包里
- You got all the cash?  - In the bag.
-哪个包?  -装着钱的那个包!
- Which bag?  - The one with the money in it!
-银行记录怎么办?   -别管它
- What about the bank records?  - Leave 'em.
-如果他们在里面找到痕迹怎么办?  -没时间了Mike
Shouldn't we sort out what they can trace?  -There is no time, Mike.
-怎么了? -你看不到吗?
What's going on?What does it look like?
我不知...
I don't...
你搞砸了John  你把我们都害了
you screwed up, John.You blew it big time.
你们在...
What are you-- what...
你们在干什么?
What are you doing?
你们要离开了吗?
Are you leaving?
为什么?这就是为什么你这个白痴!
- Why?  - That is why, you idiot!
John  你的朋友是个警察
John, your friend's a cop.
你知道我们会因为这些毒品坐多久牢吗?
You know how much jail time we'd get for this much weed?
照得不错吧  他是个刚从警校毕业的小子
Nice picture, huh? Got him fresh out of the academy.
不 他只是个搭便车的
No, he was-- He was hitchhiking.
他给我说他是要去Eureka
He told me he was going to Eureka.
他设好圈套等着你的John
He was waiting for you, John.
在这六个星期里他已经收集好证据了
He has been here for six weeks gathering evidence
-都是因为你  -这不可能
because you brought him here.- No, Mike, that's impossible.
他骗得你像个傻子  现在我们全都完了
He played you for a sucker.  -Now it's over.
不  等一下
No. Wait.
等一下  别收拾了!
Wait. No, wait, wait. Stop!
我们不知道他给他们说了什么
We don't know what he's told 'em.
他到现在都还没有进过温室
He hasn't even been in here yet.
如果他还在收集证据准备立案
If he's still gathering evidence and trying to make a case,
-那就还来得及 -来得及什么?
- then it's not too late. - Not too late for what?
保护我们  保护我们所有人
To protect us. To protect all of us.
现在干还不晚  我可以办到的
It's not too late to fix this.I can fix this.
准备怎么办John?
How are you gonna do that, John?
Eko?
John...
他没事吧?  他还活着吗
Is he okay?He alive?
把他翻过来  把他翻过来
Turn him over, turn him over.
Charlie  我们得离开这里
Charlie, we gotta get outta here.
好  把他扶起来
Okay. Let's get him up.
你说"转动钥匙"
So, when you say "turned a key,"
那是把什么钥匙?
you mean, like, a key key?
那是把应急钥匙
It was a failsafe key.
挺方便嘛
That seems kinda convenient.
什么?
I'm sorry?
我是说你有这把神奇的钥匙--
I'm just saying, if you had this magic key the whole time,
为什么却不喜欢用
why didn't you, like, use it?
我不知道用了以后会发生什么
I didn't know what would happen.
结果发生什么了?
So what did happen?
这把应急钥匙试舱门内电磁异常
Well, the failsafe key must have detonated the electromagnetic anomaly,
舱门里面结果爆炸了
made the hatch implode.
但你没有被炸
But you didn't implode.
是啊
yeah
你不会..突然就跑到那废船里面去了吧
You're not gonna, like,turn into the Hulk or something?
那就是那声巨响--
So is that what made the blender noise
和天色发紫的原因?
and the sky turn purple?
恐怕我错过了这些情节兄弟
Afraid I missed that, brother.
对  你当时在应急
Right. You were failsafing.Well, F.Y.I.,
整个岛都震动了
the whole island vibrated,
Kate  Jack和Sawyer也看到了
and Kate and Jack and Sawyer saw it, too,
在他们被抓走之前
right before they had bags pulled over their heads--
别担心  Locke演讲的时候说了他会去找他们的
Don't worry.Locke's gonna go after them.He said so in his speech.
什么演讲?什么?
-What?What speech?
他只是说他去把熊杀了救Eko回来
All he said was he was gonna save Eko and kill bears.
没错
Right.
没错...当然
Right, of course.
对不起  我...
I'm sorry. I...
我不是很清醒...
I'm just, uh, a bit shook up.
我把那头熊烧得挺厉害的
I burned that bear pretty good.
我认为它不会来追我们
I don't think he's gonna be coming after us.
现在我们在这次自杀性任务中幸存了
Now that we've survived this suicide mission,
你愿意告诉我你看到什么了吗?
do you wanna tell me what you saw?
我看到了什么?
What I saw?
在你那个神秘的帐篷里
In your spirit tent.
我看到Boone了
I saw Boone.
Boone?
他说什么了?
What did he have to say for himself?
他对我说我收拾我留下的惨剧
He told me I had to clean up my own mess.
他可能没有死吧
Well, dead as he may be,
不管怎么样我同意他的说法
I agree with Boone.
如果你照Eko说的继续按按钮--
After all, if you kept pressing that button like Eko told you to--
我们现在根本就不用救他
We wouldn't have had to save him in the first place,
对Charlie 那就是"收拾你自己留下的残局"的意思
yeah, charlie, that's what cleaning up your own mess means.
听起来好像有很多残局啊(mass和mess谐音)
Spoken like someone who's had a few too many messes to clean.
没有发现鹿吗?
No deer, huh?
没有
no
你跟Mike还有Jan说了吗?
You talk to Mike and Jan yet?
对  当然说了
Yeah, sure did.
他们觉得怎么样?
Yeah? What'd they say?
他们叫我今晚吃完饭以后带你到温室里去
They said that I should bring you by the greenhouse tonight after supper
他们会告诉你你想知道的事情
and that they would explain everything.
酷
Cool.
太棒了
That's great.
你看到什么东西了吗?
What, did you see something?
John
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你知道会是我吗?
Did you know it would be me?
什么?
What?
你知道我会开着货车经过吗?
In the truck. Did you know it would be me driving?
是他们选的我吗?
Did they choose me?
他们?  我不知道你在说什么John--
They? John, I have no idea what you're talking about--
我没有给那把枪上子弹
I didn't load that one.
回答我的问题好吗Eddie?
So how about you just answer the question, Eddie?
对
Yeah.
他们选了你John
They chose you, John.
为什么?
Why?
因为你来这里没多久
Because you hadn't been here long,
没有犯罪记录  长官说
didn't have a criminal record,and the psych profile said
你可以当污点证人
you would be amenable for coercion.
污点证人...
Amenable for coercion--
放下枪John
Lower the gun, John.
好吗?  我只是办公事
Okay? This isn't personal.
这是我们之间的事!
It's not personal?!
停下来  停下来
Stop, stop.
对不起John  你不会开枪的
I'm sorry, John, but you're not gonna shoot me.
你不是谋杀犯
You're not a murderer.
你是个好人
You're a good man.
一个农民
You're a farmer.
不
no
我不是农民
I'm not a farmer.
我曾经是个猎人
I was a hunter.
现在也是
I'm a hunter.
我现在要走了John
I'm gonna walk away now, John.
John  你听到了吗?
Hey, John. You hear something?
好像附近有河
- It sounds like a stream.
把他放下来
Let's put him down.
也许我们应该给他点水
Maybe if we get some water in him.
我去  你在这里等
I'll go. You stay here.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起以前怀疑你
Sorry I ever doubted you.
对不起对这个岛失去信念
Sorry I gave up on my faith in the island.
我把事情都搞砸了
I messed up.
现在我们的人被抓了
Now our people are captured and...
如果我听你的--
if I'd just listened to you,
如果我让你--
if I'd just let you...
继续按按钮...
keep pushing the button...
我可能就会和他们一起去了
I could've gone with them,
可以保护他们
protected them.
可以救他们
I could've saved 'em.
你仍然可以保护他们
You can still protect them...
你仍然可以救他们
you can still save them.
我连他们在哪里都不知道
I don't even know where they are.
你会找到他们的
You will find them.
因为
After all...
你是个猎人John
you are a hunter, John.
他醒了  Eko?
He's awake. Eko
也许我们该...把他带回去了John
Maybe we should just...get him back John
好
yeah
-你还行吗? -对  继续走
- You all right? - Yeah. Just keep walking.
John? Charlie?
出什么事了?
What happened?
我们找到他了
We got him.
-他还活着吗?  -应该把Jack找来
- Is he alive?  - We need Jack.
-把他抬进去   -Jack回不来了
- Take him in. - Jack's not coming back.
他们把他抓走了 -什么?  你在说什么?
- They've got him.- What?What are you talking about?
-Jack不在这里? -我听不明白
- Jack's gone? - I don't understand.
你怎么不告诉我们Hurley?
Okay, when were you planning on telling us, Hurley?
"他们"是谁?
What do you mean, "they"? Who's "they"?
"他们"就是其他人  没错  他们抓走了Jack--
"They"are the others,and yes, they've taken Jack...
还有Kate和Sawyer
and Kate and Sawyer.
怎么回事?  发生什么事了? Sun  Jin还有Sayid在哪里?
How? What happened?What about Sun and Jin and Sayid?
不知道  但我会找到我们的朋友的
I don't know.I'm gonna find our friends.
但是我会想到的
but I will.
我们会找到他们
We're gonna find them--all of them.
然后带他们回家
And then we're gonna bring them home.
但是现在最重要的是
But first things first.
我们应该照顾好Mr.Eko
We've gotta look after Mr. Eko,
Paulo  Nikki拿些毛巾和水过来
so, Paulo, Nikki, bring towels and water.
Claire  我们必须帮他洗一下身子
Claire, we gotta clean him up,
把你们能找到的急救品都带来
so bring all the first aid supplies you.
OK
不错的演讲
Not a bad speech.
哇...
"Whoa,"
哇什么?
"Whoa," what?
太不可思议了.....
Deja vu(法语 意思是似曾相识)
好吧...
ok
换好衣服后
well, when that wears off,
你能到厨房拿些绷带来吗?
can you get, bandadges,from the kitchen?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■